Finding Aid for Michigan Memorial Phoenix Project Records, 1947-2003
Bentley Historical Library
- Research, 1948-2003
  - Research Grants, Nos. 1-816, 1948-1996
    - #201-#400
      - Proposal for Adding Information on the International Peaceful Uses of Atomic Energy to the World Handbook of Political and Social Indicators, R. Hefner, [387.] (Box 44)
      - Study of Structure and Synthesis of Isozymes in Human Reticulocytes and Leukocytes, G.J. Brewer, [388.] (Box 44)
      - Acoustical Wave Propagation in Steam-Water Mixtures, L.J. Hamilton, [389.] (Box 44)
      - Offset Beam Port Collimator-Monochromator, J.S. King, [390.] (Box 44)
      - Fission Cross Section Measurements with Photoneutron Sources, G.F. Knoll, [391.] (Box 44)
      - Study of Regulations of Invertase by Gibberellic Acid in Avena Internodes, P.B. Kaufman, [392.] (Box 44)
      - Radiation Sterilization of Suspensions, L.L. Kempe, [393.] (Box 44)
      - Development of Test Systems to Determine the Sensitivity of Neoplasms to Alkylating Agents, J.M. Johnson, [394.] (Box 44)
      - A Preliminary Study of the Skeletal Collection from the Thebian Tombs of the New Kingdom Period (1570-1080 B.C.), J.E. Harris, [395.] (Box 44)
      - Plasma Clearance of Labeled Amino Acids, R.S. Kowalczyk, [396.] (Box 44)
      - Development of a Radioimmunoassay for Estraiol, G.D. Niswender, [397.] (Box 44)
      - Effects of a Constrictor Agent and a Dilator Agent on Calcium Movement in Rabbit Aortic Strips, D.F. Bohr, [398.] (Box 44)
      - Cytogenetic Investigation of Patients Treated with "Superficial" X-irradiation for Benign Skin Disease, A. Bloom, [399.] (Box 44)
      - Activation Analysis of Thyroid Hormones in Tissue Cell Components, F.L. Hoch, [400.] (Box 44)
    - #401-#600
      - Transplacental Transfer and Fetal Distribution of 14C Labeled Anti-Thyroid Drugs in the Pregnant Dog, W. Beierwaltes and J.D. Quinones, [401.] (Box 44)
      - Diet-related Strontium Content in Human Bone, C.L. Brace, [402.] (Box 44)
      - Neutron Scattering in Liquid Helium II, H. Gould and V.K. Wong, [403.] (Box 44)
      - High Resolution Photoelectron Spectroscopy, H. Griffin and L. Lohr, [404.] (Box 44)
      - Inertia Stresses in Rapidly Heated Reactor Fuel Rods, J.J. Hamilton, [405.] (Box 44)
      - Effects of Nuclear Radiation on Superheats to Nucleate Boiling Liquids, F.G. Hammitt, [406.] (Box 44)
      - Mossbauer Effect Study of Fast Neutron Irradiation Effects in Copper-Rich Cu-Fe Alloys, D.H. Vincent, [407.] (Box 44)
      - Wear of Apatite Surfaces by Activation Analysis of Wear Fragments, R.G. Craig, [408.] (Box 44)
      - Preparation of 32 P-Labeled Nucleoside Phosphates and Sugar Nucleotides by Neutron Activation, G. Jourdian and J. Distler, [409.] (Box 44)
      - Plasma Protein Metabolism in Dysproteinemic Disorders, M. Votaw and J. Penner, [410.] (Box 44)
      - A Test of Charge Conjugation Invariance, A. Rich, [411.] (Box 44)
      - Cortisol Assay by Competitive Protein Displacement, D.E. Schteingart, [412.] (Box 44)
      - A Search for the Inelastic Scattering of Thermal Neutrons from Isomeric States of Nuclei, J.M. Carpenter, [413.] (Box 44)
      - Forensic Uses of a Portable X-Ray Spectrometer Using Radioisotope X-Ray Sources, A.A. Gordus, [414.] (Box 44)
      - The Influence of Serotonin, Resperpine, and Para-Chlorophenylalanine on Radiation Effects in Mammals, A.P. Jacobson, [415.] (Box 44)
      - Development of Hyperparathyroidism and Osteodystrophy Secondary to Renal Insufficiency, R.D. Johnson, [416.] (Box 44)
      - Sodium Transport into Cerebrospinal Fluid, D.S. Luciano, [417.] (Box 44)
      - The Use of Algae for Removal of Radioactive Materials from Liquid Wastes, P.A. Plato, [418.] (Box 44)
      - Investigation of Mechanisms Controlling Platelet Production, J.A. Penner and R. Reed, [419.] (Box 44)
      - Radiography of Cryptic Biological Systems in Trees, J.R. Thornbury, [420.] (Box 44)
      - Application of Radioisotopes to the Study of Lattice Dynamics and Structures of Ionic Solids, B.J. Evans, [421.] (Box 44)
      - A Photographic Study of the Hydrodynamic Mechanisms Relevant to Forced Convection, Subcooled Boiling Burnout as Applied to Pressurized Water Nuclear Reactors, F.G. Hammitt, [422.] (Box 44)
      - Search for X-ray Sources Among the Flare Stars, W.A. Hiltner, [423.] (Box 44)
      - Thermal Neutron Micro-Radiography, G.F. Knoll, [424.] (Box 44)
      - High Resolution Autoradiography of Brain, B.W. Agranoff, [425.] (Box 44)
      - Autoradiographic Studies on Tissue Culture Cells Following Laser-microirradiation of Chromosomes and Mitochondria, M.W. Berns, [426.] (Box 44)
      - In Vivo Renal Glucose Production in Rats, P.C. Churchill, [427.] (Box 44)
      - The Source of DNA Precursor Incorporated into Trophoglast, A.D. Floyd, [428.] (Box 44)
      - Recombination as a DNA-repair Process, R.B. Helling, [429.] (Box 44)
      - Study of Mechanisms for the Regulation of Vascular Smooth Muscle Intracellular Calcium Concentration, C. Seidel, [430.] (Box 44)
      - Enhancement of Viral Susceptibility of Cultured Mammalian Cells Irradiated Continuously with Low-Level 60 Gamma Radiation, C. Shipman, [431.] (Box 44)
      - Peaceful Nuclear Proliferation: New Dimensions of an Old Problem, L. Scheinman, [432.] (Box 44)
      - 'Partial' Arms Control Measures in International Law Perspective, E.Stein, [433.] (Box 44)
      - Thermal Neutron Radiation Damage Center, C. Kikuchi, [434.] (Box 44)
      - Use of Nuclear Explosions to Test a New Method of Locating Earthquake Epicenters Precisely, R. Van der Voo, [435.] (Box 44)
      - Investigations on the Role of the Cell Wall in the Growth of Oat Stem Segments, P. Adams, [436.] (Box 44)
      - Studies of 64Cu-Labelled Pink Copper-Protein from Human Erythrocytes, D.E. Hultquist, [437.] (Box 44)
      - Development of a 32P-33P Double Label Technique for Monitoring Changes in Protein Phosphorylation, L.J. Kleinsmith, [438.] (Box 44)
      - Mercury Analysis in Aquatic Ecosystems, G.E. McBride, [439.] (Box 44)
      - An Analysis of the Response Pattern of a Perturbed Diurnal Oscillatory Control Mechanism in the Algal and Bacterial Plankton of Lakes, G.W. Saunders, [440.] (Box 44)
      - Visualization of Myocardium with 123I Oleic Acid Albumin Complex, J.C. Sisson, [441.] (Box 44)
      - Trace Element Analysis of Prehistoric Chert Resources in Oaxaca, Mexico, E.N. Wilmsen and K.V. Flannery, [442.] (Box 44)
      - Abundance Analysis of the Peculiar A Star HR 465, C.R. Cowley, [443.] (Box 44)
      - High Resolution in Vivo Monitoring of Low Energy Emitters, J.Bardwick, [444.] (Box 44)
      - Scavenging of Trace Metal Ions by Ferromanganese Oxides, E. Callender, [445.] (Box 44)
      - Permanently Drag Reducing Tubes, J.H. Hand, [446.] (Box 44)
      - Time Correlations of Nuclear Gamma Rays, R.R. Lewis, [447.] (Box 44)
      - Applied Field Mossbauer Spectrometer, R.H. Sands, [448.] (Box 44)
      - Red Cell Survival Measurements, D. Aminoff, [449.] (Box 44)
      - Studies of Labeled Iron-ATP Complexes of Mammalian Erythrocytes, G.J. Brewer, [450.] (Box 44)
      - The Effects of X-Irradiation Upon Morphogenesis in the Regenerating Limb, B.M. Carlson, [451.] (Box 44)
      - Effects of Diet, Physical Training and Detraining on the Rate of 14C-Acetate Incorporation into Tissue Lipids, M.L. Foss, [452.] (Box 44)
      - Mechanism of Action of Luteinizing Hormone in the Bovine Corpus Luteum, K.M.J. Menon, [453.] (Box 44)
      - Influence of New World Silver on the European Economy in the 16th and 17th Centuries, A.A. Gordus, [454.] (Box 45)
      - Study of Physical Security Options in a Nuclear Safeguards System for the Civilian Nuclear Powers Industry in the United States, R.H. Williams, [455.] (Box 45)
      - Theoretical Studies of Electron Thermal Conduction in Laser-Heated Plasmas, J.J. Duderstadt, [456.] (Box 45)
      - Application of Radioisotopes to Studies of Novel and Important Catalysts in the Plastics Industry: 121SB and 238U Nuclear-Gamma-Ray Resonance of U-Sb-O Acrylonitrile Catalyst, B.J. Evans, [457.] (Box 45)
      - Glassy Carbon--Elastomer Composites, J.H. Hand, [458.] (Box 45)
      - Mossbauer Effect Study of Fast Neutron Irradiation Effects in Copper-Rich Cu-Fe Alloys, D.H. Vincent, [459.] (Box 45)
      - Neutron Activation Analyses of Serum Gold Levels-A Guide to Treatment of Patients with Rheumatoid Arthritis, G.G. Bole, [460.] (Box 45)
      - A Micro Method for the Qualitative and Quantitative Measurement of Connective Tissue Mucopolysaccharides, G.W. Jourdian, [461.] (Box 45)
      - Isolation and Identification of a New Plasma Glycolipoprotein, E.A. Napier, [462.] (Box 45)
      - Quantitation and Treatment of Potassium Deficiency in Patients with Chronic Obstructive Pulmonary Disease with Chronic Respiratory Insufficiency, J.G. Weg, [463.] (Box 45)
      - Flow Oscillations Associated with Nucleation Characteristics in Forced Convection Boiling, H. Merte, [464.] (Box 45)
      - NMR Determination of the Nuclear Magnetic Moment and Absolute Nuc. Screening Constant of Lead-207, R.R. Sharp, [465.] (Box 45)
      - Genetic Regulation in Cultured Eucaryotic Cells, C.J. Chetsanga, [466.] (Box 45)
      - The Development of a New Carbon Fixation Technique for the Measurement of Primary Production in Alkaline Saline Lakes, P. Kilham, [467.] (Box 45)
      - Determination of Lymphocyte -- Mediated Cytotoxicity by Release of Radioactivity from Labeled Viable Cells, J.E. Niederhuber, [468.] (Box 45)
      - DNA and RNA Synthesis by a Unique Virus, A.R. Price, [469.] (Box 45)
      - Development of a Radioimmunoassay for the Detection of IgE Antibodies to Human Microbial Pathogens, P.Steinberg, [470.] (Box 45)
      - Chert Resources and Interaction Patterns During the Late Archaic and Late Woodland in Michigan, E.N. Wilmsen, [471.] (Box 45)
      - Earthquake Resistance of Nuclear Power Plants, R.D. Hanson, [472.] (Box 45)
      - Activation Analysis of Thyroid Hormones in Mitochondria Components, F.L. Hoch, [473.] (Box 45)
      - Feasibility and Development of a Correlative Technique in X-ray Image Formation: The Stochastic Filter, A.Z. Akcasu, [474.] (Box 45)
      - Diffusion of Tritium in Metals and Alloys, D.H. Vincent, [475.] (Box 45)
      - Localization of Protein Inhibition in Monkey Brain, B.A. Agranoff and C.M. Butter, [476.] (Box 45)
      - Responsiveness of the Cyclic Ovine Ovary to Endogenous Gonadotropic Stimulation, B.G. England, [477.] (Box 45)
      - Cellular Autophagy as a Biological Accommodation Mechanism of Repair After Exposure to Ionizing Radiation, R.H. Gray, [478.] (Box 45)
      - Activation of Enzymes Forming Precursor Nucleotides of Bacterial Virus DNA, G.R. Greenberg, [479.] (Box 45)
      - A New Diabetogenic Peptide from Human Pituitary Glands, L.H. Louis, [480.] (Box 45)
      - Amino Acid Transport in Virus Transformed 3T3 Mouse Cells, D.L. Oxender, [481.] (Box 45)
      - Retention of Fallout Radionuclides in the St. Joseph River Watershed, P. Plato, [482.] (Box 45)
      - Predictions of Masses of Unknown Nuclear Species Based on Generalized Nuclidic Mass Relationships, J. Janecke, [483.] (Box 45)
      - Crystal Structure Measurements by Neutron Diffraction, J.S. King, [484.] (Box 45)
      - Combined Theoretical and Observational Investigation of Quasi-Stellar Objects, G.M. MacAlpine, [485.] (Box 45)
      - Regional Cerebral Blood Flow Using Radioactive Microspheres, L.G. D'Alecy, [486.] (Box 45)
      - The Action of Gibberellic Acid on Cell Wall Synthesizing Enzymes in Oat Stem Internodes, H. Ikuma, [487.] (Box 45)
      - Microtubule Function and Sensory Transduction, R. Schafer, [488.] (Box 45)
      - Dynamics of Growth Hormone Secretion of Patients with Diabetes Mellitus, R.P. Knopf, [489.] (Box 45)
      - A Determination of the Myocardial Concentration Dependence of the Ammonium Compounds, B.R. Lucchesi and F.J. Kniffen, [490.] (Box 45)
      - Development of a Packed-Bed Photochemical Reactor, B. Carnahan, [491.] (Box 45)
      - The Significance of Bacteria in Lake Eutrophication: Bacterial Cycling of Algal Carbon, D.P. Chynoweth, [492.] (Box 45)
      - 18-hydroxydesoxycorticosterone Assay in Human Hypertension, E.L. Cohen, [493.] (Box 45)
      - Growth of the Goldfish Retina, S.S. Easter, [494.] (Box 45)
      - Turnover Rate of Cytochrome P and of Proteins of the Bile Canalicular membrane after Ethynyl Estradiol Administration to Rats, J.J. Gumucio, [495.] (Box 45)
      - Biochemical Adaptation in Muscle, G.H. Jones, [496.] (Box 45)
      - Prolactin Receptors and Luteal Cell Function, J.S. Richards, [497.] (Box 45)
      - Nuclear Power: A Challenge in Public Consumer Education, C. Kikuchi, [498.] (Box 45)
      - Isotopic Mixed Organic Phosphors, R. Kopelman, [499.] (Box 45)
      - Effective Range for the Power Distribution Monitoring Systems in the Light Water Reactors, J.C. Lee, [500.] (Box 45)
      - Mossbauer Effect of 67Zn and Its Application to the Study of Zinc-Containing Proteins, R.M. Polichar, [501.] (Box 45)
      - Radioiodination of Proteins with Special Reference to Sulfhydryl-Sensitive Proteins, I.J. Goldstein, [502.] (Box 45)
      - Luxury Accumulation of Trace Metals by Various Algae: Its Significance in Algal Succession, Eutrophication and Mercury Pollution, K. Porter, [503.] (Box 45)
      - Analysis of Site II Photophosphorylation, C. Yocum, [504.] (Box 45)
      - Characterization of a Copper-X-Globulin Complex Isolated from a Patient with Hypercupremia and Immunoglobulinemia, D.E. Hultquist, [505.] (Box 45)
      - Determination of Dissociation Rates of DNA-anti-DNA Complexes in Systemic Lupus Erythematosus, R.E. Petty, [506.] (Box 45)
      - Algorithms for Fault Tree Analysis, A. Rosenthal, [507.] (Box 45)
      - In Vitro Surfactant Secretion by Fetal Pneumonocytes, R.C. Borer, [508.] (Box 45)
      - Insertion of Tryptophan Operon of E. coli into SV40 DNA, D.A. Jackson, [509.] (Box 45)
      - Surface Antigens of Mouse Fibroblast Cells, H. Rittenhouse, [510.] (Box 45)
      - The Acoustic Receptor of the Noctuid Moth as a Biochemical Model of Hearing, J. Schacht, [511.] (Box 45)
      - Abnormal Methylation of Transfer RNA in Preconvulsant Brain Cells, O. Sellinger, [512.] (Box 45)
      - Radioisotope Labeling of Phosphoryl Acceptor Site of (Na+ + K+) -- Adenosine Trip. w/ Tritiated Borohydride, G.J. Siegel, [513.] (Box 45)
      - Use of 203Pb to Study the Renal Handling of Lead, D.R. Mouw and A.J. Vander and Heat Production Measurements in Selected Rock Suites, D. Chapman and D. Meyer, [514.] (Box 45)
      - Trace Metal Associations in the Organic Fraction of Lacustrine Sediments, R.M. Owen, [515.] (Box 45)
      - Particle to Gas Conversion and the Measurement of Gaseous HC1, D.H. Stedman, [516.] (Box 45)
      - Metabolism of Activated Human Synovial Cells, C.W. Castor, [517.] (Box 46)
      - Cyclic Guanosine 3'5' Monophosphate in Bacterial Physiology: Isolation and Study of cGMP-Binding Proteins, D.A. Chambers, [518.] (Box 46)
      - Virulence Determinants of Salmonella Typhimurium, G. Jones, [519.] (Box 46)
      - Pharmacologic Protection of the Ischemic Myocardium-Determination of Regional Coronary Blood Flow with Radioactive Microspheres, B.R. Lucchesi, [520.] (Box 46)
      - Characterization of Concanavalin A Receptors from Animal Cells by Surface Labeling, H.G. Rittenhouse, [521.] (Box 46)
      - Diagnosing Formation Conditions of Alkalic and Gabbroic Intrusives Using Trace Elements in Magnetites, P.L. Cloke, [522.] (Box 46)
      - Noise Analysis in Power Reactors, Z. Akcasu, [523.] (Box 46)
      - An Investigation of the Low Temperature Spectra of NO2 Trapped in Gamma-Irradiated KC1 Crystals, A.H. Francis, [524.] (Box 46)
      - Geology, Mineralogy and Rare-Earth Geo-chemistry of the Barringer Hill Pegmatite District, Llano and Burnet Counties, Texas, E. William Heinrich, [525.] (Box 46)
      - Cyclic AMP and Differentiation in Dictyostelium Discoideum, S. Cooper, [526.] (Box 46)
      - Neuroanatomical Correlates of the Hippocampal Theta Rhythm, P. Coyle, [527.] (Box 46)
      - Investigation of the Degradation of Luteinizing Hormone-Releasing Hormone by Pituitary Tissue, J.C. Marshall, [528.] (Box 46)
      - Transport of CNS (Central Nervous System) Drugs in Neural Cells in Culture and into Brain in vivo, F. Medzihradsky, [529.] (Box 46)
      - An Investigation of the Role of Cellular Immunity in Human Liver Disease, M. Mutchnick, [530.] (Box 46)
      - Investigation of Tritiated Horseradish Peroxidase as a Retrograde Transport Marker, R.G. Northcutt, [531.] (Box 46)
      - Microphotometric Analysis of Lymphocytes Present in Rejecting Kidney Tissue Grafts, D.T. Freier, [532.] (Box 46)
      - Studies on Silicon Deposition in Sugarcane Using Neutron Activation Analysis and Energy Dispersive X-ray Microanalysis, P.B. Kaufman, [533.] (Box 46)
      - Studies on an Enzyme Complex Involved in the Regulation of Folate Metabolism, R. Matthews, [534.] (Box 46)
      - Characterization of an Algal Toxin, P.G. Meier, [535.] (Box 46)
      - Radioimmune Detection of Antigens Shed from Tumor Cells, H. Rittenhouse, [536.] (Box 46)
      - Radioisotope Studies of Background Bromide Levels and Their Importance in the Formation of Brominated Organics During Water Treatment, M.S. Simmons, [537.] (Box 46)
      - Stratigraphy and Paleoecology of Western Snake River Plain, G.R. Smith, [538.] (Box 46)
      - The Reconstruction of Diet and Social Status in Prehistoric Human Populations, C. Loring Brace, [539.] (Box 46)
      - An Early Warning System Simulation for Cross-Overs Between Peaceful and Military Nuclear Development, C. Kelleher, [540.] (Box 46)
      - Identification of Salinity-Specific Proteins in the Fish Gill by Isotopic Labeling, B.A. Doneen, [541.] (Box 46)
      - Feedback Control of Brain Cyclic AMP by a Ca++-Binding Protein, M.E. Gnegy, [542.] (Box 46)
      - The Effects of the Hydrogen Ion Concentration on Gradient and Membrane Potential on Catecholamine Transport into Chromaffin Vesicles, R. Holz, [543.] (Box 46)
      - Regulation of Angiotensin II Levels in Cerebrospinal Fluid of the Dog, M.G. Nicholls, [544.] (Box 46)
      - Reproductive Effort and Its Relationship to Life History and Ecology, D.W. Tinkle, [545.] (Box 46)
      - Rapid K/Ar Age Determination by Activation Analysis, P.L. Cloke, [546.] (Box 46)
      - Study of Nuclear Masses and Pairing Vibrations, W. Gray and R. Tickle, [547.] (Box 46)
      - Gold and Silver Abundances in Porphyry Copper Deposits, S.E. Kesler, [548.] (Box 46)
      - Uranium Recovery from Chattanooga Shale, G.B. Williams, [549.] (Box 46)
      - Generalized Nonsubstitution Models of Depletable Resources, H.R. Varian, [550.] (Box 46)
      - High Energy Radiotracers: Applications in Nuclear Medicine, J.W. Keyes and W.L. Rogers, [551.] (Box 46)
      - Does Cadmium Induce the Synthesis of Metallothionin in Mouse Liver and Testis, M.H. Meisler, [552.] (Box 46)
      - A Study of Enrichment of Cis-Phylloquinone in Liver Mitochondria, M.J. Thierry-Palmer, [553.] (Box 46)
      - A Four-Circle Neutron Diffractometer, J.S. King, [554.] (Box 46)
      - Application of the Finite Element Method to the Neutron Transport Equation, W. Martin, [555.] (Box 46)
      - A Search for Stable Negative Ions of Helium, J.C. Zorn, [556.] (Box 46)
      - Nuclear Energy: The Structure of the Movement and Counter-Movement, [557.] (Box 46)
      - Opiate Receptor Binding Properties in Discrete Brain Regions and Spinal Cord of Two Inbred Mouse Strains Displaying Pharmacogenetic Differences in Narcotic Responsiveness, E.F. Domino, [558.] (Box 46)
      - Studies on Measles Virus Persistent Infections, L.E. Fisher, [559.] (Box 46)
      - Involvement of a Ca++-Binding Protein and Protein Phosphorylation in Dopaminergic Supersensitivity in the Striatum, M.E. Gnegy, [560.] (Box 46)
      - Krypton-81m: Clinical Application for Non-invasive Analysis of Right Ventricular Function, J.H. Thrall, [561.] (Box 46)
      - Neurochemical Correlates of Spasticity, A.B. Young, [562.] (Box 46)
      - Definition of an Optimized, Special Purpose Processor for Coded Aperture Tomography in Nuclear Medicine, D.E. Atkins, [563.] (Box 46)
      - Development of Cryogenic Targets for Heavy-Ion Research, F. Becchetti, [564.] (Box 46)
      - Mossbauer Study of Carthaginian and Their Corrosion Products, B. Evans, [565.] (Box 46)
      - Solitons and Strong Turbulence in Plasmas, R.S.B. Ong, [566.] (Box 46)
      - Functional Anatomy of the Basal Ganlia, J.B. Penney, [567.] (Box 46)
      - The Influence of Muscular Activity and Dietary Restriction on Skeletal Muscle Glycogen Repletion, T.P. White, [568.] (Box 46)
      - Nuclear Magnetic Resonance Studies of Two-Dimensional Quantum Systems, M. Bretz, [569.] (Box 46)
      - Trapping and Diffusion of Hydrogen and Helium in Metals, D.H. Vincent, [570.] (Box 46)
      - Uranium-Thorium-Rare Earth Element Partitioning Between Pegmatites & Their Parent Granites, B.H. Wilkinson, [571.] (Box 46)
      - B-Endorphin --MSH: Receptor Studies & Chromatographic Separation, H. Akil, [572.] (Box 46)
      - Molecular Events in the FGRF-mediated growth Control of Cultured Mouse Cells, P. Datta, [573.] (Box 46)
      - Transfer RNA Methyltransferase Activities During Hormone Controlled Cell Differentiation, J. Heady, [574.] (Box 46)
      - Isolation of SV40 Viral Transcription Complexes, L. Lutter, [575.] (Box 46)
      - Cell Free Transcription of the Alpha-fetoprotein Gene, D. Miller, [576.] (Box 46)
      - An Economical Synthesis of Uridine Diphoso Glucose, N. Radin, [577.] (Box 46)
      - Search for an Endogenous Activator of Adenylate Cyclase Associated with Protein I, as synapse-specific phosphoprotein, T. Ueda, [578.] (Box 46)
      - Federal-State Concurrence and Nuclear Waste Disposal, M.K. Jennings, [579.] (Box 46)
      - Role of camp in Regulation of Brain Capillary Permeability, A.L. Betz, [580.] (Box 46)
      - Biochemistry of Exocytosis from Chromaffin Cells, R.W. Holz, [581.] (Box 46)
      - Mechanisms of Microbial Halogenations, G.T. Sperl, [582.] (Box 47)
      - Evaluation of Cardiac Function in Diabetes Mellitus: Effect of Hyperglycemia as a Myocardial Depressant, J.H. Thrall, [583.] (Box 47)
      - Calcium and Vascular Smooth Muscle in Hypertension, R.C. Webb, [584.] (Box 47)
      - Study of Radiation Effects in Molybdenum by Positron Annihilation, D.H. Vincent, [585.] (Box 47)
      - Popular Support for the Pro-and Anti-Nuclear Movements, M.N. Zald, [586.] (Box 47)
      - Neuronal Development: Ciliary Ganglion Cell Surface Antigens, K.F. Barald, [587.] (Box 47)
      - Actin-membrane interaction, S. Brown, [588.] (Box 47)
      - Genetic Variation in Mitochondrial DNA, W. Brown, [589.] (Box 47)
      - DNA sequences involved in the Heavy Chain Switch, W. Dunnick, [590.] (Box 47)
      - Asphyxia and the Developing Brain: Selective Vulnerability of Chemical Neurotransmitter Systems, M.V. Johnston, [591.] (Box 47)
      - Plasma Heating and Current Generation by Microwave, R.M. Gilgenbach, [592.] (Box 47)
      - Low Temperature Electrical Resistivity of Pyrolytic Graphite and Its Dilute Intercalation Compounds, C. Uher, [593.] (Box 47)
      - The Economic Costs of Nuclear Waste Disposal, T.C. Bergstrom, [594.] (Box 47)
      - Site-Specific Mutagenesis of Viral DNA's, W. Folk, [595.] (Box 47)
      - Isolation and Characterization of Proteins Synthesized During Recovery of Cd2+-exposed E. coli, R.S. Mitra, [596.] (Box 47)
      - Evolution of the Gene Coding for Alcohol Dehydrogenase in Drosophila, G.P. Moore, [597.] (Box 47)
      - Identification of Receptor Components of Histamine Action, A.I. Vinik, [598.] (Box 47)
      - Measurement of Low-Energy Stopping Powers for Helium in Silver and Gold, D.H. Vincent, [599.] (Box 47)